[{"answer": "Yeah, I am", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "that place keeps its vehicles too long. If a car's over twent", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I'm in that place on the 12th, my friend on the 13th, that place on the 15th", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No, but I'll be in that place by the 20th", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Any Southwest? I'm swinging through that place the week of the 16th", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Mr. my friend, I'm here today to inform you that your position is no longer available", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yes, you're fired", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I'm fired", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Never say fired", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Hel", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " No... We're making you irrelevant", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "We prepare the newly unemployed for the emotional and physical hurdles of job hunting while... Minimizing potential legal blowback", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Okay, what are we doing", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "It's ten million miles", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Pi is just a number", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Do they give you a parade or something? 48", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Men get such a har", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " You never want to get married? Never want kids", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Yes. Yes it is", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " What a weasely prick", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "We all fall for them. Pricks are spontaneous, unpredictable, and fun. And then we're surprised when they turn out to be pricks", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Protocol is always tricky", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Sometimes there really is no right thing to do", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You thinking of going to see her", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What kind of relationship do you have", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Think there's any future there", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Really never thought about it", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Don't you think it's worth giving her a chance", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "A chance at something real", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Wow. Big words", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Well, screw you too", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I wish I was here with better news, however your position here at Deckers is no longer available", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You've been let go. 76", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I couldn't", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "You want me to be your date", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "What do you want me to do", "docId": "Up-in-the-Air.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "You want me to talk to him? 94", "qsentId": 38}]